is victor reed ruiz inducted by dr alex
johnson alex johnson is the fourth
president of kylewood community college
since becoming president in 2013 he has
led the college to record graduation
numbers while strengthening the core
mission of providing affordable access
to higher education
thank you so very much uh
really humbled by that round of applause
and certainly appreciative
that i am with you this evening
um
kyle the community college is so proud
to support the cleveland international
hall of fame and joining me
uh tonight is a number of my
colleagues
and among them
are some of our board members including
anne franknose who is our vice chair
helen forbes field the newly appointed
president of cleveland's ywca is our
chair helen congratulations to you
and of course victor ruiz
who has been celebrated this evening and
for the past 20 years he has been
an influential organizational and civic
leader
in our great city
he advocates for the educational needs
of cleveland's latinx community and he
has raised millions of dollars because
college scholarships in support of this
work
our friend victor was recognized as a
cringe cleveland power 150
one of the 500 most influential people
in northeast ohio
and a 40 under 40 young man
under his watch esperanza was cited as a
bright spot in education by the white
house initiative
on educational excellence for hispanic
his past chair
of tri-c and one of my nine bosses
certainly not bad for a man whose first
job was at mcdonald's
where he learned
the importance of teamwork and civic
engagement
but first and foremost
he is a family man
who met his lovely wife danielle
when they were 16.
they were married in age 29
and all three children were in the
wedding
alex antoine
antonio i'm sorry and katrina
because they were waiting uh to ensure
that they
could invite
their
entire families to the
celebration
despite regularly working 12-hour days
he always found time
in the evening to hang out with his
children
playing basketball and video games
here's a noted real master whose ribs
are legendary how many of you chasing
raise your hand you have all right you
need supply ribs for everybody
now there is a sentiment written by
american poet henry reward feature for a
man who has mastered
the delicate balance between family and
work
and it says
a man's ledger
does not tell
what he is
or what he is worth
count what is man
not what is on him
you would know what he is worth
ladies and gentlemen
mr victor
[Applause]
[Music]
come ruiz
thank you for those words alex you know
uh saturday my wife's like i have a
conference call
9 a.m on a saturday i'm like that's
pretty honest she just told me it was
with alex johnson to give him all the uh
on the inside baseball so
thank you for those kind of words thank
you to the hansons for
their commitment to multiculturalism
and
what the power of diversity and how it
makes us all better and this is a
special evening and i just i landed with
this i've never had an event where so
many people that i love were here for me
from my family
to my friends to my colleagues and
that's that's just makes it extra
special for me so thank you
[Applause]